Yohana Zarief Hozain

Senior Land Surveyor

PRIV + 965-51529997

□ yohana.zarief@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/yohana-zarief



SUMMARY:

A highly experienced and qualified Senior Land Surveyor with over 17 years In The Oil and Gas Industry and Infrastructure, Roads and Concrete Construction Earth works, and Drafting for complex projects. Proven Ability To Manage and Execute surveying Operations across various Sectors, ensuring precision and accuracy in all tasks. Successfully worked across multiple countries, contributing to the Successful completion of large-scale infrastructure and construction projects.

PERSONAL DATA:

CURRENT ADDRES: Al Salmiya - Abu Dhar Al-Ghifari St, block 12 lane 21, Kuwait.
 MAIN ADDRES: Alexandria, Egypt 18 Sobhy Abdelrahman St, Elseyof Victoria.

- DATE OF BIRTH: 3rd June 1986.

- PLACE OF BIRTH: Alexandria – Egypt.

NATIONALITY: Egyptian.
SOCIAL STATE: Married.
MILITARY SERVICE: Exemption.

DRIVING LICENSE: Valid Driving License In Kuwait & Egypt
 RESIDENCE: Have Kuwait Residence Visa NO. (18)

EDUCATION:

September 2003 - May 2007

ALEXANDRIA UNIVERSITY- FACULTY OF ARTS.

Bachelor's Degree from The Department of Geography (Cartography & Survey Branch)

GRADUATION GRADE: Good
 4TH YEAR GRADUATION: Good

PROJECT OF GRADUATED: Map of contour in (valley of Kharoba) in Marsa Matruh,
 Egypt

GRADUATION PROJECT GRADE: Excellent

JOB PROFILE:

- More than 17 years experiences in survey filed.
- Supervision of Construction Activities
- Fixing of Bench Marks And Traversing For New Project
- Extensive knowledge of land surveying methods and measurement practices.
- Ensured That All Required Survey Information Was Collected Per Project Requirements.
- Prepared Initial Sketches of Areas Before Any Excavation Work Took Place.

- Calculated Height Depth Width Distance And Other Key Factors.
- Checking And Recording Of Final Grading Levels For As Built. Coordination To Clients Engineers, Consultant Engineers Regarding Site Situation Etc...
- Checking of Profile, Cross-Section And Setting Out.
- Setting out of Centerline For Earthwork, Sub Base, Base Material And Pavement Of Highways.
- Setting out from building foundation up to roof slab, Box Culverts, Pipe Culverts, And Slab Culverts.
- Architectural Drafting.
- Solid understanding of geometry engineering and trigonometry.
- Strong on the following surveying soft wares
- Proficient on (Civil Mechanical Electrical Infrastructure Roads) Surveying.
- Impressive analytical and conceptual abilities.
- Excellent internal and external communications skills.

APPROVER LIST

- Have Four approval from Kuwait oil company (KOC)
- Have one approval from Kuwait University
- Have one approval form Ministry of Electrical and Water

LANGUAGES skills

- Arabic: Native.
- English: Good (written and spoken).

COMPUTER SKILLS

- Surveying Expert
- Surveying devices (Level Machine, Total Station and GPS) Expert
- Measurement analysis Expert Problem solving Expert
- Site inspections Expert
- Auto Cad Civil 2D V. GOOD
- Auto Desk Civil 3D GOOD
- MS office V. GOOD
- Surfer- V.GOOD

INSTRUMENTS

- All Types of Level Instruments
- o Total Station Leica (TC1200 TC1100 TCR1203 & TC 405)
- Total Station Sokkia (600 610 power set cx series ...)
- Total Station FOIF Topcon
- GPS Leica 1200 viva
- GPS Trimble R4S

WORK EXPERIENCE

Professional Experience More Than 17 Years

FROM JULY 2023 TILL NOW:

11 PATTERNS WELL HOOK-UP & ASSOCIATED WORKS NORTH KUWAIT

• COMPANY: Sayed Hamid Behbehani & sons co. (SHBC) W.L.L

OWNER: Kuwait Oil Company. (KOC)
 FIELD OF WORK: Consulting of civil Surveyor

FROM SEP 2022 TO JUNE 2023:

REPLACEMENT OF UNDER GROUND PIPELINE NETWORK FOR FIREFIGHTING &SERVICE WATER AND POTABLE WATER SYSTEMS AT DOHA WEST POWER STATION

&WATER DISTILLATION PLANT

COMPANY: HYDROTEK ENGINEERING COMPANY

• OWNER: Ministry of electricity &water

• FIELD OF WORK: Replacement of three type of Underground pipeline

FROM OCTOBER 2017 TO SEP 2022:

CONCTRUCTION OF 11 KV ELEVATED MAIN INTAKE SUBSTATION

B4,B5 & MG-2 IN S&EK AREA

• COMPANY: KCCEC Engineering & Contracting (KUWAIT) W.L.L.

• OWNER: Kuwait Oil Company. (KOC)

• FIELD OF WORK: Three Substation building, Three main Access road, power cable rote, Fibre Optical Cable Rote & culverts .. etc

FROM MAY 2016 TO SEPTEMBER 2017:

SHUWAIKH CAMPUS STAFF HOUSING RENOVATION BLK.#4

• COMPANY: KCCEC Engineering & Contracting (KUWAIT) W.L.L.

• OWNE: Kuwait University- construction & maintenance dept.

FIELD OF WORK: Building, Ac and plumping work and land scape ... Etc

FROM FEBRUARY 2015 TO DECEMBER 2017:

CONCTRUCTION OF NEW ELEVATED 11KV MAIN INTAKE (72MW)

SABRIYA (C) SUBSTATION

• COMPANY: KCCEC Engineering & Contracting (KUWAIT) W.L.L.

• OWNER: Kuwait Oil Company. (KOC)

• FIELD OF WORK: Building, Access Road, Fibre Optical Cable Rote, Firefighting Piping Work Finishing Work ... Etc

FROM MAY 2013 TO FEBRUARY 2015:

NEW 11KV 72 MK MAINBULK INTAKE SUBSTATION

AT RAWDATHAIN - (D) & SABRIYA - (B) AREA

• COMPANY: O & G Engineering W.L.L. for General Trading & Contracting

• OWNER: Kuwait Oil Company. (KOC)

• Field Of Work: Substation Building, Access Road, Cable Rote & Culvert ... Etc

FROM AUGUST 2012 TO APRIL 2013:

Mina Al Ahmady Refinery

NEW AGRP / AGRP REVAMP PROJECT

• COMPANY: Gulf Dredging & General contracting co.

• OWNER: Kuwait National Petroleum Company . (KNPC)

CONSULTANT: Tecnimont

• FIELD OF WORK: West Water Area, Pipe Racks, Tanks, Vertical Vessel, Horizontal Vessel, Under Ground Piping ...Etc

FROM JUNE 2011 TO AUGUST 2012:

NEW BOOSTER STATION BS 171 WEST OF KUWAIT

• COMPANY: Gulf Dredging & General contracting co.

• OWNER: Kuwait Oil Company. (KOC)

CONSULTANT: Flour - Saipem

 Field Of Work: Pipe Rack From 1 To13, Hp - Lp Flare, Incinerator, Pipe Sleeper, Culvert, Burn Pit Area, Vertical Vessel, Horizontal Vessel, Valve Pit, Duct Bank, Control Building, Substation Building, Security Building, Concrete Tanks, Steel Tanks, Sum Pit, Nitrogen and Hp - Lp Compressor Foundation

FROM DECEMBER 2009 TO MAY 2011:

"ABU QIR THERMALPOWER PLANT UNITS 6 & 7"

• COMPANY: ORASCOM Construction Industries – Besix (j v)

• OWNER: WEST DELTA ELECTRICITY PRODUCTION COMPANY (WDEP.CO)

• CONSULTANT: (PGESCO) power generation engineering and services co.

• FIELD OF WORK: Piles Work, Stem Turbine Unite 6-7, Water Treatment Area, R.C.C.P Underground Piping, Transformer, Tanks And Pipe Rake

FROM JULY 2008 TO NOVEMBER 2009:

"SIDIKIRIR POWER STATION COMBINED CYCLE 750 M W"

• COMPANY: ORASCOM Construction Industries – Besix (j v)

• OWNER: WEST DELTA ELECTRICITY PRODUCTION COMPANY (WDEP.CO)

• CONSULTANT: (PGESCO) Power Generation Engineering and Services co

• FIELD OF WORK: Many Building like (In Take Pump House, C. W. Electric Building, Sell Well Building, Hypochlorite Sodium) and R.C.C.P Underground Piping

FROM JANUARY 2008 TO JULY 2008:

"ARAB MALL PROJECT"

• COMPANY: ORASCOM Construction Industries

OWNER: Egyptian centre for Real estate development
 CONSULTANT: (ECG) Engineering Consultants Group

• FIELD OF WORK: Check levelling for back filling layer, foundation, Anchor bolt, construction building from excavation up to finishing work and steel structure building

FROM JUNE 2007 TO DECEMBER 2007:

• Training in Oscar company for piles in Alexandria

Courses History

- ICDL
- AutoCAD 2007 2D
- OSHA (Occupation Safety and Health Administration)

Interests / Activates:

- Sports, Travelling, Reading, Like To Gain Knowledge.
- Like To Visit So many Countries around the World and I have No Problem to Work in Any place in the world.

Thanks for your Appreciation